

ACHIEVEMENTS

- KSN Informatika 2020 Silver Medalist
- **National Training of IOI** Top 16 of Indonesia

Falcon Programming UPH

2019 3rd Place Finish

Dcode10 Competitive Programming Contest 3rd Place Finish

CONTACT

- ☆ Cirebon
- **(**021) 203408
- 082214093455
- ✓ Andrewjeremy12345@gmail.com
- in andrew.jeremy
- andrew.jeremy
- © +62 82214093455

ANDREW JEREMY

UNDERGRADUATE IN UNIVERSITY OF INDONESIA

A BIT ABOUT MYSELF

An undergraduate at the University of Indonesia, majoring in Computer Science. Taught potential KSN participants for 3+ years. Authored and Organized an international Competitive Programming contest with over 280 participants. Competed and studied Competitive Programming for 3+ years.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present Supervisor for KSN Informatika 2021

Supervisor

Preparing contests and simulations to help KSN participants familiarize themselves to

KSN environment.

2020 - Present **Kokokoder Coaching Service**

Coach

Coached over 15 KSN participants, 10 of whom became prestiged medalists

2020 - 2021 **Penabur Science Club Training**

Coach

Coached over 30 students. Helped them learn necessary topics for KSN preparation.

2020 - 2021 **SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong Science**

Camp

Coach

Coached over 4 students in preparation of KSK over the course of 3 days. Prepared contests and went over the solution for each problems.

2019 - 2020 17th TOKI Regular Open Contest

Author and Contest Organizer

Made an internationally recognized contest that had over 280 participants. Authored and made necessary preparations for each of the

problems.

SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong 2018 - Present

Part-time Teacher

Taught a few students Competitive Programming by teaching topics necessary for KSN and preparing training materials/ contests

for the students taught.

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

University of Indonesia

Depok

Computer Science

2018 - 2021

SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong

Kab. Tangerang Brilliant Class

PROJECTS

2020

17TH TOKI REGULAR OPEN CONTEST

Indonesia's Informatics Olympiad Team
Started this project in 2018, started out by making a few problem ideas, which were developed over time. Made test cases, editorials, and Problem Statements for the contest. The contest ran for 2 hours and had a total of 289 international

participants.

2019

BRILLIANT COMPETITION WEBSITE

Penabur National Science and Math Competition
Started a project of making a public website for
SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong's Brilliant
Competition, which is a nationwide Science and
Math Competition. Used a combination of HTML,
CSS, and Javascript to maintain the website.